Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office. Information Center Records, 1901-2005 and undated RL.11121
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2018 Additions, 1901-2006 and undated; 1
  - Advertising Awards and Festivals, 1965-2006; 3
    - Excellence in Advertising on Television (EAT) Awards, 1987 (Box 56)
    - Harry Wayne McMahon 100 Best, 1967-1982; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Institute of Outdoor Advertising, 1965-1970 (Box 56)
    - International Advertising Festival of New York, 1986-1987 (Box 56)
    - International Advertising Film Festival (Cannes), 1968-1972; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - International Advertising Film Festival (Cannes), 1973-1984; 6 folders (Box 57)
    - International Broadcasting Awards, 1966-1984; 8 folders (Box 57)
    - International Film and Television Festival of New York, 1966-1984; 5 folders (Box 57)
    - Lists of awards won, 1967-1971 (Box 57)
    - London International Advertising Awards, 1986 (Box 57)
    - MPA Kelly Awards, 1991 (Box 57)
    - O&R (Objectives and Results) Awards, 1983 (Box 57)
    - One Show, 1981-1986; 4 folders (Box 57)
    - Stephen E. Kelly Award (MPA), 1982-1986; 4 folders (Box 57)
    - USTV Commercial Festival, 1982 (Box 57)
    - U.S. TV and Radio Commercials Festival, 1984 (Box 57)
    - Video Storyboards Awards, 1988-1993 (Box 57)
    - Windy Awards, 1982 (Box 57)
  - General Files, 1933-2001 and undated; 4
    - Bringing Day One to Life, 1995 (Box 58)
    - Chicago advertising agencies, 2001 (Box 58)
    - Chicago Office credentials, undated (Box 58)
    - Chicago Office--IBM computers, 1985 (Box 58)
    - Chicago Office--Guide to Written Communications, undated (Box 58)
    - Commodore's Cup, 1993-1995; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Consumer in Crisis seminar, 1974 (Box 58)
    - Food Facts & Foibles (newsletter drafts), 1933-1939 (Box 58)
    - James Webb Young Award, 2000 (Box 58)
    - JWT Advertising Planning Methods, 1987 (Box 58)
    - JWT Axiom Market Research, 1973-1978 (Box 59)
    - JWT case studies binder--Chicago, 2001; 2 folders (Box 59)
    - JWT case studies binder--Other offices, 2001; 2 folders (Box 59)
    - JWT Chicago history, undated (Box 59)
    - JWT Communications Program review, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 59)
    - JWT credentials: 133 Years of Advertising Leadership, 1997 (Box 60)
    - JWT Guide to Research, 1990 (Box 60)
    - JWT history, 1985-1993 (Box 60)
    - JWT Internal and External Communications Plan, 1976 (Box 60)
    - JWT T-Plan, 1977 (Box 60)
    - Look at JWT Chicago, undated (Box 60)
    - Microfilm index, undated (Box 60)
    - "New Work" video index, undated (Box 60)
    - Research and Planning Department Policies and Procedures Manual, 1971-1979; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Slides and photographs--JWT Traveling Archives exhibit for Dairy Association pitch, 1993 (Box 61)
    - Slides and photographs--Softball games, parties, 1980-1981 (Box 61)
    - Slides and photographs--Office spaces, 1969 (Box 61)
    - Statements of research philosophy, 1961-1962 (Box 61)
    - "Thompson Papers" secretarial manual, 1985 (Box 61)
    - VALS (Values and Lifestyles Program) reports, 1980-1983 (Box 61)
  - Human Resources-Related Files, 1960-1996 and undated; 5
    - Directories, 1968-1979; 5 folders (Box 61)
    - Directories, 1976-1996; 4 folders (Box 62)
    - Employee assistance program, 1985 (Box 62)
    - Employee benefits (manuals), 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Employee benefits highlights, undated (Box 62)
    - Equal employment/Affirmative action, 1977 (Box 62)
    - Managerial feedback program, 1977-1978 (Box 63)
    - Memos, 1960-1989; 4 folders (Box 63)
    - New employee orientation, 1987; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Performance appraisal process, 1977 (Box 63)
    - Training Program for the JWT Trainee in Creative, 1965 (Box 63)
  - Printed Materials, 1963-2000; 6
    - 100 Books on Advertising, 1976 (Box 64)
    - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies)--Advertising Principles of American Business, 1988 (Box 64)
    - AAAA--Effectiveness of Web Addresses in Ads, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Advertising Agency New Business Planning Guide, 1978 (Box 64)
    - Advertising and the Government, 1971 (Box 64)
    - Advertising Expenditures--International Comparisons 1960-1975, 1977 (Box 64)
    - Advertising Expenditures in Western Europe, 1972-1977; 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Adweek 20th anniversary issue, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Arbitron Radio Multi-Week Cume Rule, 1985 (Box 64)
    - ARF (Advertising Research Federation)--Interactive Media Research Summit, 1998 (Box 64)
    - ARF--Last Word in Print, 1998 (Box 64)
    - ARF--Television Research in Analog, Digital and High Definition, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Brouillard study of corporate reputations, 1986 (Box 64)
    - Byron Hackett--How to Keep Your Ads Out of Court, 1974 (Box 64)
    - Consumers Research--In Praise of Advertising, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Coupon Trends and Consumer Usage Patterns, 1995 (Box 64)
    - Donnelley Survey of Promotional Practices, 1995 (Box 64)
    - Effective reach tables, 1981 (Box 64)
    - Household Use of Information Technologies--Australia, 1996 (Box 64)
    - Innovation and Brand Choice: The Folger's Invasion, 1963 (Box 64)
    - Jacobs Coffee Concept Test in the U.S., 1988 (Box 64)
    - JWT--Advertising and Marketing Intelligence brochure, 1980 (Box 98)
    - JWT--Advertising during a Recession, 1983 (Box 65)
    - JWT Basic Advertising Course (William Sharp), 1969 (Box 65)
    - JWT--Humor: Its Serious Side, 1972 (Box 65)
    - JWT--Magazine reach curves, 1981 (Box 65)
    - JWT--People Meter reach manual, 1987 (Box 65)
    - JWT--Role of Account Management at JWT, 1986 (Box 65)
    - Thompson Total Branding brochure, 1996 (Box 65)
    - JWT-- TV Guide for Media Planning, 1980 (Box 65)
    - JWT--TV Reach and Frequency System, 1989 (Box 65)
    - Leo Burnett--Reach and Frequency, 1986 (Box 65)
    - Louis Harris--Advertising Agency Reputations, 1986 (Box 65)
    - Management of an Accounting Practice Survey, 1995 (Box 65)
    - Manual of Reach and Frequency, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Margaret Henderson Blair--Empirical Investigation into Advertising Wearin and Wearout, 1987 (Box 65)
    - Measurements and Determinants of Brand Equity, 1986 (Box 65)
    - Microwave Market and Opportunities for Nestle Foods, 1988 (Box 65)
    - National Association of Broadcasters--Code News, 1976-1982; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - NBC Radio Research, 1979 (Box 66)
    - Ogilvy--Advertising, Sales Promotion and the Bottom Line, 1989 (Box 66)
    - Psychology Today, 1985 Nov. (Box 66)
    - Product Alert (serial), 1996-1997; 16 folders (Box 67)
    - Product Alert 1996 Round-Up, 1997 (Box 67)
    - Radio Advertising Bureau--Instant Background Profiles, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Readership Research Symposium Proceedings, 1981 (Box 67)
    - Readership Research Symposium Proceedings, 1981-1985; 7 folders (Box 68)
    - Readership Research Symposium Proceedings, 1985-1991; 8 folders (Box 69)
    - Review of U.S. Coffee Market, 1987 (Box 70)
    - Roper reports, 2000 (Box 70)
    - Sears Roebuck Late Night Television 1977-1978 (Box 70)
    - Sports Reach Manual, 1981-1982 (Box 70)
    - Starch/Hooper Media Study, 1970 (Box 98)
    - Starch Study of Affluence in America, 1997 (Box 70)
    - Television reach and frequency, 1974 (Box 70)
    - Town and Country--Buying Luxury, 1998 (Box 70)
    - Travel Industry Association of America--Crisis Communication Manual, 1990 (Box 70)
    - TV Reach & Mixit, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Speeches, Writings, Presentations, 1908-2002 and undated; 7
    - Arno Johnson, 1959-1961; 6 folders (Box 71)
    - Arno Johnson, 1961-1964; 7 folders (Box 72)
    - Arno Johnson, 1964-1966; 4 folders (Box 73)
    - Arno Johnson bibliography, 1966 (Box 73)
    - Charles Raymond--Story of Early JWT in Chicago, 1956 (Box 73)
    - Don Sullivan--Trends in the Last Decade of the 2nd Millennium, 1990 (Box 73)
    - Ellen Plusker--Role of Research in an Ad Agency, undated (Box 73)
    - Ellen Plusker--Speaking the Right Language, 1986 (Box 73)
    - Harnessing Consumer Choice, 2002 (Box 73)
    - Heat is On: Does Advertising Still Work?, undated (Box 73)
    - Infomercials: Transactional Television Programming, 1993 (Box 73)
    - Joel Baumwoll--Is Comparative Advertising Really Better?, 1975 (Box 73)
    - Malachy Walsh--What Is Strategy?, 2002 (Box 73)
    - Malachy Walsh--Yin and Yang of Consumer Insight, undated (Box 73)
    - Mike Kalasunas--The Bottom Line: Achieving Results, 1988 (Box 73)
    - Norman Strouse, 1958-1965; 9 folders (Box 74)
    - Norman Strouse, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 75)
    - Philippine Market, 1961-1967; 3 folders (Box 75)
    - Simplify Surprise and Sell, 2001 (Box 75)
    - Sonia Yuspeh--Product Life Cycle, 1976-1977 (Box 76)
    - Ted Wilson talks about advertising and the government, 1971 (Box 76)
    - Thought for Food, 1983; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Unlocking the Power of Consumer Insight, 1995 (Box 76)
    - Speeches and articles chronological file, 1908-1956; 23 folders (Box 77)
    - Speeches and articles chronological file, 1957-1968; 27 folders (Box 78)
    - Speeches and articles chronological file, 1969-1976; 25 folders (Box 79)
    - Speeches and articles chronological file, 1976-1979; 18 folders (Box 80)
  - Subject File, 1909-1999 and undated; 8
    - Account management assignments, 1966-1978; 3 folders (Box 81)
    - Advertising--Appeals, 1969-1982 (Box 81)
    - Advertising--Appeals--Scent, 1990-1994 (Box 81)
    - Advertising--Art, 1958-1961 (Box 81)
    - Advertising--As a profession, 1958-1984; 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Advertising--Children, 1979-1992 (Box 81)
    - Advertising--Comparative, 1975 (Box 81)
    - Advertising--Cooperative, 1958-1993 (Box 81)
    - Advertising--Economic aspects, 1957-1994 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Effectiveness, 1988-1995 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Ethics, 1964-1972 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Ethnic, 1965-1970 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Expenditures, 1977-1994 and undated; 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Exposure, 1909-1995 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Frequency, 1957-1983 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Historical, 1985-1987 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--History--Children, 1962-1976 and undated (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Industrial, 1974-1977 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Institutional, 1974-1983 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--International, 1964-1991 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Legal aspects, 1960-1974 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Long-lasting campaigns, 1984-1992 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Media models, 1962 (Box 82)
    - Advertising--Readership, 1940-1979; 4 folders (Box 83)
    - Advertising--Sex and gender, 1987-1993 (Box 83)
    - Advertising agencies, 1961-1997 (Box 83)
    - Advertising agencies--Client relations, 1958-1987; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Advertising agencies--Client relations, 1970-1987; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Advertising agencies--Compensation, 1956-1983; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Advertising agencies--Creativity, 1985-1992 (Box 84)
    - Advertising agencies--Finance, 1980 (Box 84)
    - Advertising agencies--House agencies, 1939-1979; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Advertising agencies--Image and awareness, 1984-1990 (Box 84)
    - Advertising agencies--Minorities, 1968-1969 (Box 84)
    - Australia, 1954-1978 (Box 84)
    - Belgium, 1960-1977 (Box 84)
    - Brands, 1975-1997 (Box 85)
    - Canada, 1970-1977; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Chicago articles distributed by G. Reeves, 1960-1964 (Box 85)
    - Chicago Office press clippings, 1929-1980 (Box 98)
    - Chicago Office Ralph Rydholm house advertisement, 1981 (Box 98)
    - Chicago traffic, 1961 (Box 85)
    - Children/Kids in advertising (Jane Matthews, JWT London), 1992-1993 (Box 85)
    - Communispond, 1970-1977 (Box 85)
    - Computer installations, 1962-1969 (Box 85)
    - Computer Panel, 1952-1960 (Box 86)
    - Consumer affairs, 1923-1974 (Box 86)
    - Consumer behavior, 1991-1998 (Box 86)
    - Consumer in Crisis seminar, 1974; 4 folders (Box 86)
    - Consumer values, 1990-1994 (Box 86)
    - Corporate communications, 1975-1979 (Box 86)
    - Corporate image, 1993 (Box 86)
    - Database marketing, 1984-1992 (Box 87)
    - Deltakos, 1968-1975 (Box 87)
    - Detroit, 1970-1978 (Box 87)
    - Dialog, 1973-1975 (Box 87)
    - Diogenes, 1974 (Box 87)
    - Direct response marketing, 1973-1975 (Box 87)
    - Employment by occupation, 1992 (Box 87)
    - Entertainment Group, 1979 (Box 87)
    - Family Advisory staff, 1959 (Box 87)
    - Financial aspects, 1969-1972; 4 folders (Box 87)
    - Financial aspects, 1973-1977; 5 folders (Box 88)
    - Financial aspects, 1969 (Box 97)
    - Food, 1987-1999; 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Food--Bubble gum, 1990-1992 (Box 88)
    - Food--Labels, 1992-1993 (Box 88)
    - Food--Milk, 1981-1993; 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Foreign offices--London--EMRB, 1973 (Box 88)
    - Foreign offices--Miscellaneous, 1965-1979 (Box 88)
    - Frankfurt, 1954-1960 (Box 88)
    - History of JWT--Charles Raymond, undated (Box 88)
    - History of JWT--Policy, philosophy, etc., 1956-1971; 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Home Economics Center, 1958-1979 (Box 89)
    - Home Economics Center, undated (Box 98)
    - Household appliances, 1985-1988 (Box 89)
    - India, 1972-1978 (Box 89)
    - International information services, 1968-1971 (Box 89)
    - Italy, 1978 (Box 97)
    - Joseph Wood campaign research, 1970 (Box 89)
    - Joseph Wood campaign research, 1968-1970 (Box 97)
    - Junior Forum, 1951-1952; 2 folders (Box 89)
    - JWT Worldwide Research Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 89)
    - London Office, 1964-1979 (Box 89)
    - London Office, 1968-1978; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - London Office--BMRB, 1966 (Box 89)
    - London Office--Research reports, 1968-1969 (Box 89)
    - London Office--Times Supplement, 1962 (Box 98)
    - Marketing--Database, 1991-1992 (Box 89)
    - Marketing--Integrated, 1987-1993 (Box 89)
    - Marketing--Sales promotion--Popai, 1995-1996 (Box 90)
    - Media, 1986-1998; 2 folders (Box 90)
    - Media--Communications Review, 1982 (Box 90)
    - Media Department, 1977-1978 (Box 90)
    - National co-op surveys, 1976-1977 (Box 90)
    - New business, 1968-1979 (Box 90)
    - New products evaluation, 1971-1972 (Box 90)
    - New York Office, 1958-1970 (Box 90)
    - New York Office--Magazine Notes, 1970-1973 (Box 90)
    - New York Office--Personnel memos and lists, 1964-1975 (Box 91)
    - New York Office--Research Department, 1960-1982; 2 folders (Box 91)
    - New York Office--War Room, 1980 (Box 91)
    - Plan and Data Outlines, 1924-1960; 2 folders (Box 91)
    - Pricing, 1987-1994 (Box 91)
    - Public relations, 1976 (Box 91)
    - Public relations activities, 1970-1971 (Box 91)
    - Public relations activities, 1972 (Box 92)
    - Public Relations Department slides, 1963-1978 (Box 92)
    - Public service activities, 1976 (Box 92)
    - Publications--Media Memo, 1969-1973 (Box 92)
    - Publications--Media Memo, 1970 (Box 97)
    - Publications--Memo from Media Research, 1982-1987; 3 folders (Box 92)
    - Publications--Memo from Media Research, 1982-1987 (Box 93)
    - Publications--PR Department Magazine Reading Reports, 1969 (Box 93)
    - Radio commercials, 1972 (Box 93)
    - Real estate, 1996-1998 (Box 93)
    - Research and Development activities, 1976-1992 (Box 93)
    - Research Department, 1963-1976 (Box 93)
    - Research Department--Floor plan, John Hancock Building, 1968 (Box 98)
    - Research Department--Marketing Man of the Year dinner, 1964 (Box 93)
    - Research Department--Policies, 1969-1971 (Box 93)
    - Research Department--Seminars and meetings, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 93)
    - Retail, 1988-1993 (Box 93)
    - Review Board, 1963-1971 (Box 94)
    - San Francisco Office, 1920-1977 (Box 94)
    - Seminars, 1978 (Box 94)
    - Services Department, 1977-1978 (Box 94)
    - Soskin-Thompson, undated (Box 94)
    - South Africa, 1974-1979; 2 folders (Box 94)
    - Sporting goods, 1984 (Box 94)
    - Target Group Index #1, 1972-1976; 4 folders (Box 94)
    - Target Group Index #1, 1972-1976 (Box 95)
    - Target Group Index #1, 1972-1976; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - Target Group Index #2, 1972-1977; 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Target Group Index Creative News survey, 1971-1978 (Box 95)
    - Telecommunications, 1973-1979 (Box 95)
    - Television--Reach and frequency, 1970-1971 (Box 95)
    - Television--Violence and boycotts, 1977-1980 (Box 96)
    - Television--Workshop, 1958-1961 (Box 96)
    - Women--Car buyers, 1991 (Box 96)
    - Women--Health and fitness, 1993 (Box 96)
  - Research Department Card Files, Undated; 9
    - A-Cook Chemical, undated (Box CF1)
    - Coors-G. McKlosky & Co./Theodore Hamm, undated (Box CF2)
    - McCollum/Spielman: Abbott Labs-Quaker Oats Dog Food, undated (Box CF3)
    - Quaker Oats Dog Food-Sears Roebuck, undated (Box CF4)
    - Sears Roebuck-Vopan Marketing Research/S.C. Johnson, undated (Box CF5)
    - Uncle Ben's-Zenith Radio, undated (Box CF6)
    - Misc. reports: X1 Advertising Agencies, undated (Box CF6)
    - X2 Advertising Research, undated (Box CF6)
    - X3 Advertising Media, undated (Box CF6)
    - X4 Sales Promotion, undated (Box CF6)
    - X6 Markets and Marketing, undated (Box CF6)
    - X7.1 Foods, undated (Box CF6)
    - X8 JWT, undated (Box CF6)
    - X9 New Business, undated (Box CF6)
    - Staff Profiles (Name, office, start date?), undated (Box CF7)
  - Numbered Research Reports, 1919-1988 and undated; 10
    - T66-C-20.5-A. Kellogg Triple Crisps, 1985; 3 folders (Box R1)
    - T66-C-22-A. Kellogg Brown Rice Crunch, 1986; 2 folders (Box R1)
    - T66-C-24-A. Kellogg Calcium Crisp, 1986 (Box R1)
    - T66.35-C-7-ABC. Study of 6 Concepts for Puss 'n Boots New Shark Meat Cat Food, 1969 (Box R2)
    - T66.35-H-1-A. Puss 'n Boots Case Study, 1966 (Box R2)
    - T66.35-H-1-A. Puss 'n Boots Fact Book, 1968 (Box R2)
    - T66.35-M-1-A. Puss 'n Boots Marketing Plan, 1965 (Box R2)
    - T66.35-M-1-A. Quaker Oats Summary of Dry Cat Food Market, 1968 (Box R2)
    - T66.35-M-2-ABC. The Cat Food Market, 1971 (Box R2)
    - T66.35-M-10-A. Summary of Available Information on the Cat Food Market, 1965 (Box R2)
    - T66.37-C-10-A. Aunt Jemima Syrup New Product Quantitative Concept Test, 1987 (Box R2)
    - T66.37-C-10.1-A. Quaker Oats--Consumer Reaction to Alternative Concepts for Aunt Jemima Syrup, 1987 (Box R2)
    - T66.37-C-10.2. Aunt Jemima Syrup New Product Quantitative Concept Test, 1987 (Box R2)
    - T66.37-C-10.3-A. Aunt Jemima Lite Syrups ARS Test of "Mom and Dad", 1987 (Box R2)
    - T66.37-C-11-A. Aunt Jemima Syrup Line Extensions Concept Test, 1987 (Box R2)
    - T66.39-C-2-A. Dipps Restage Attitude, Awareness and Usage Study, 1987 (Box R2)
    - T72.1-A-10-A. Northern Telecom Campaign Review, 1988 (Box R3)
    - T72.1-C-1-A. Reputation of Northern Telecom among Four Key Groups, 1981 (Box R3)
    - T72.1-C-1-C. Reputation of Northern Telecom among Four Key Groups, 1981; 2 folders (Box R3)
    - T72.1-C-10.1-A. Northern Telecom Starch Scores, 1984 (Box R3)
    - T72.1-C-13.05-A. Awareness and Attitudes Toward Northern Telecom's Meridian Line, 1985; 3 folders (Box R3)
    - T72.1-C-13.11-A. Assessment of Northern Telecom Building Blocks Campaign, 1985; 3 folders (Box R3)
    - T72.1-C-14-AB. Northern Telecom Image Measurement Program, 1986 (Box R3)
    - T72.1-C-17-AB. Research Study on Northern Telecom Image, 1986 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-C-18-AB. Research Study on Northern Telecom Image, 1986 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-C-19-AB. Research Study on Northern Telecom Image, 1986 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-C-21-A. Northern Telecom Tracking Study, 1987 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-C-27-A. Study of Top Level Executive Media Habits for Northern Telecom, 1987 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-C-28-A. Northern Telecom Image, 1987; 2 folders (Box R4)
    - T72.1-D-1-A. Northern Telecom--Northeast Electronics Division Qualitative Attitudinal Research, 1984 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-D-2-A. Central Digital Equipment Supplier Attitudinal Study, 1985 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-D-3-A. Central Digital Equipment Supplier Attitudinal Study, 1985 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-D-4-A. Central Digital Equipment Supplier Attitudinal Study, 1985 (Box R4)
    - T72.1-D-7-A. Northern Telecom Readership Study, 1988 (Box R5)
    - T72.1-D-8-B. Northern Telecom Campaign Review, 1988 (Box R5)
    - T72.1-M-1-A. Northern Telecom Competitive Advertising Review 1982-1984, 1985 (Box R5)
    - T75.1-A-1-A. Ameritech Revised 1983-1984 Communications Objectives (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-0.01-A. Highlights of a Focus Group Among Institutional Investors and Retail Brokers, 1983 (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-0.02-A. Ameritech Summary of Results--Qualitative Communication Check of 1983 Print Advertising (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-1-A. Ameritech National Ad Tracking Study, 1983 (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-2-A. Ameritech Proposal for Research: Qualitative Communication Check of 1984 Regional Television Advertising, 1983 (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-3-A. Ameritech National Ad Tracking Study, 1983 (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-3.1-A. Ameritech Regional Awareness and Tracking Study, 1984 (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-4-A. Ameritech Name Study, 1985 (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-4.1-A. Ameritech Regional Awareness and Attitude Tracking Study, 1985 (Box R5)
    - T75.1-C-5-AB. Ameritech Regional Awareness and Attitude Tracking Study, 1986 (Box R5)
    - X1-2. Making Advertising Pay During the Depression, 1932 (Box R6)
    - X1-4. Training for JWT Service, 1919 (Box R6)
    - X1-11-ABC. JWT Chicago Advertising Agency Profile, 1979 (Box R6)
    - X1-12-AB. Corporate Image: Corporate vs. Brand, 1984 (Box R6)
    - X1-13-A. Economics clipping file, 1984 (Box R6)
    - X1-14-A. Advertising agencies clipping file, 1984; 2 folders (Box R6)
    - X1.5-1-A. Marketing clipping file, 1984 (Box R6)
    - X1.5-2-A. Advertising agency trends, 1984 (Box R6)
    - X1.6-2. Report on Investigation Among Chicago Grocers, undated (Box R6)
    - X1.6-6-A. Using Means-End analysis of Consumer Motivation to Develop Effective Advertising Strategies, 1986 (Box R6)
    - X2-5. Copy Is Our Product, 1960 (Box R6a)
    - X2-40-A. Advertising Research (AMA short course), 1976 (Box R6a)
    - X2-40.1-A. Fundamentals and Applications of Marketing Research, 1977; 2 folders (Box R6a)
    - X2-40.2-A. Analysis of Television and Consumer Promotion Tests, undated; 2 folders (Box R7)
    - X2-40.3-A. MSA Diary Panel Seminar, 1979; 4 folders (Box R7)
    - X2-40.31-A. Practical Use of Research in Marketing, 1978 (Box R7)
    - X2-40.4-ABC. JWT Research: Philosophy, Systems and Case Histories, 1979 (Box R8)
    - X2-41-ABC. JWT Approach to Advertising Research, 1979 (Box R8)
    - X2-42-ABC. Advertising Research, 1979 (Box R8)
    - X2-43-ABC. JWT Research, undated (Box R8)
    - X2-44-ABC. JWT Approach to Advertising Research, 1979 (Box R8)
    - X2-45-ABC. Guide to Research Alternative Creative Strategies, 1979 (Box R8)
    - X2-45.1-AB. Advertising Research, 1980 (Box R8)
    - X2-45.2-A. A Systematic Approach to More Effective Advertising Pre-Testing Research, 1980 (Box R8)
    - X2-46-A. Advertising Agency Group Research: Applications and Philosophies, 1980 (Box R8)
    - X2-47-AB. Diffusion of Innovation, 1982 (Box R8)
    - X2-48-A. Discussion of Advertising Wearout, 1985 (Box R8)
    - X2.1-.01-ABC. Researching Advertising Audiences, 1959 (Box R8)
    - X2.2-2.1-A. Marlboro Print Ad, 1964 (Box R8)
    - X2.2-3-ABC. Copy Evaluation As We See It, 1957 (Box R8)
    - X2.2-4-A. Measuring the Effects of JWT Advertising Campaigns, 1962 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-5-ABC. Proposal for Post Measurement of Advertising in a Normal Reading Situation, 1962 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-6-ABC. Brand Image Case Histories, 1966 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-6.1-A. Evaluation of Television Commercials, 1966 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-7-A. JWT Magazine Pre-Testing System, 1969 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-8-AB. Quickie Fact Sheets, 1969 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-9-A. JWT Viewpoint on Pre-Testing, 1972 (Box R9)